[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[theme music playing]
TAKE CHARGE OF MY HEART
[romantic music playing]
[distant sirens wailing]
[music intensifies]
[music softens]
Miss Na,
I don't wanna just protect you anymore.
What?
Na Bo-bae…
I'm crazy about you.
[romantic Korean ballad playing]
[romantic Korean ballad continues]
[music softens]
[Miss Na] Stupid slow motion. Ugh…
This is taking way too long.
[kissing]
[Miss Na kissing]
[Miss Na grunting]
Come on!
Hm?
So this is what lips feel like?
-[quack] -[gasps]
Oh!
[dramatic music playing]
[grunts sleepily, gasps]
[sniffles, sighs]
Oh no, I was dreaming about my script again? [sighs]
Seriously, even in my dreams, I manage to get writer's block?
I couldn't even get to the kiss part?
[tuts, sighs]
Oh shoot.
[lively music playing]
THE CITY WITHOUT LIGHTS
THE FINAL CHAPTER, AGAIN
So if I were the main character in a drama,
this is how I'd be introduced.
-[man grunts] -[Miss Na groans]
-Bo-bae, hurry up and get ready. -[Bo-bae] Okay!
[Korean pop music playing]
[Bo-bae] Meet Na Bo-bae.
A woman who's pushing 30
with no clear plan for the future.
[groans]
Ji-hye, where's my hoodie? You know my checkered one?
Oh, I put it outside.
[Bo-bae] That's my older sister,
a soon-to-be-married national tae kwon do gold medalist.
-Hey, Yong-gi! -[Yong-gi] Yeah?
Throw it over!
-This one? -[Bo-bae] Yeah
Here!
[Bo-bae] That's my older brother,
a national judo medalist who now owns his own dojo.
And then, there's me,
the youngest and the only writer in a family of athletes.
CONTEST AWARD ONE-EP DRAMA
Luckily, my family has always loved me and supported me,
despite my rather unusual condition.
[grunts]
Heading out!
-[Yong-gi] You're leaving? -Yeah.
[Ji-hye] You're almost 30 now. How are you still always late for work?
-Wait! -[Ji-hye] Breakfast!
-I don't want it. My stomach hurts… -Come on, open up, Bo-bae.
-[Yong-gi] Just eat. -My stomach hurts.
-[Ji-hye] Nonsense. Eat it slowly. -I'm going.
You see, I'd left home to chase writing career,
boldly promising my parents I'd crawl back if I didn't make it by 30.
Make it happen!
[Bo-bae] So these days, I'd say I'm walking a tightrope,
always teetering on the verge of failure.
[crackling]
[pop music fades]
[gasps] Ow, jeez.
[grunts]
[bus brakes squeal]
Oh… Uh!
Um… [gasps softly]
[whimpers]
Oh no… [whimpers uncertainly]
[uneasy music playing]
[stop bell dings]
-[suspenseful music playing] -[electricity crackling]
[music fades]
[Bo-bae breathing nervously]
[whimpering unsteadily]
-[yelping unsteadily] -[suspenseful music playing]
[gentle music playing]
[Bo-bae] Wow, he's incredibly good-looking.
[gasps softly]
A guy like him would be perfect as a leading man.
Oh, no, not, like, my leading man or anything.
I mean, like a leading man in one of my scripts.
[brakes screech]
[Bo-bae screams]
[sweeping romantic music playing]
[heartbeat pounding]
You… okay there?
[Bo-bae] If this were a drama,
this would be the start of our love story.
Uh…
[Bo-bae] But for me, this isn't a love story.
It's a horror show.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
-Because… -Ow, that hurts!
…romance doesn't exist for a girl like me.
But it does for the girl in my scripts.
[confident music playing]
HYE-JU STRIDES AWAY
Miss Hye-ju, please.
(WITH A BURNING GAZE) MA'AM!
[suspenseful music playing]
Why did you follow me on the bus?
I told you, I didn't need you to escort me to work.
How could I not follow you? I can't stop thinking about you.
Well, I won't stand for this inappropriate behavior.
Start acting like my bodyguard.
AS HYE-JU TURNS TO WALK AWAY, I-HYEOK GRABS HER ARM
[suspenseful music building]
I-HYEOK PULLS HER INTO A ROUGH KISS
HYE-JU IS STARTLED AT FIRST, BUT SOON MELTS INTO THE KISS
[breathlessly] Your lips are delectable. They taste like honey.
[feistily] Your lips taste good as well.
[music stops]
What kind of mess is that?
Oh!
-What now? -It's always the kissing scenes with you.
Lips taste like honey? What were you thinking?
Is this guy a bear? Why would he point that out?
And a bodyguard can't just kiss their boss like that. It's unprofessional.
-Or maybe dangerous. -Sure, maybe it looks good on paper.
But we live in a woke era now. You need to get with the times.
I mean, this male lead, he's been her bodyguard for only two weeks.
So why would he risk his job to kiss a woman he barely even knows?
I mean, isn't that what you do when you fall in love?
When you know, you know…
I mean, you'd risk anything to make them yours
and your brain gets all fuzzy when they're around--
Miss Na.
Please be honest with me.
Have you ever been on a date?
What? Come on.
-I'm almost 30 now. -[awkward music plays]
How could you ask me such a thing? I mean…
[man] Oh really? So you've been on dates before?
You've been on romantic amusement park dates
and Hangang River walks?
I'll have you know… I've done it all. That's just the tip of the iceberg.
I used to have guys lining up for me back in the day.
Oh, really? So what did all that amount to exactly?
Look at the poor lead in this.
He didn't just kill the romance in this script.
He ran it over and backed up again.
[Bo-bae] Of course it's bad.
I'm so chronically single that I bolt if a guy so much as touches my hand.
Seriously, the rest is okay.
At the start of your career, everyone wanted a piece of you,
but I called first dibs on your work.
Your lines are great. The story's great. The leads three-dimensional.
But why do they turn into a mess the minute there's romance involved?
You're betraying your viewers.
It's like you're stabbing them right in the heart.
You know that's not my intention.
[man] Look, your contract ends in three months.
You do want to renew it, don't you?
Yeah.
-[dreamy music playing] -Three months, okay.
I'm giving you three whole months
to write a steamy love story
Grab a person off the street for inspiration if you have to.
A sexy romance.
[awkward music plays]
You get me that, okay?
Yeah.
-[strong wind blowing] -[uneasy music playing]
TS RESORT, JEJU
[people screaming]
Oh shit!
-[grunting] -[women yelling]
Ah, I think the rain got in my mouth!
[all yelling]
[man] Where are we even going?
-That way! -Why won't they just pick up the phone?
[squeals]
["Clair de Lune" playing]
[cell phone buzzing]
Yes? Are you almost there?
You can head up now.
Get the cameras ready.
[man sniffs, sighs]
[distant sirens wailing]
TS RESORT, SEOUL
[woman] Who's telling him about what's going on at the Jeju resort?
Human Resources should handle it. It was flagged by the general manager.
No, anything regarding reservations should be handled by the Rooms department.
[uneasily] Oh jeez.
Well, I can picture it now.
That smug little know-it-all picking everything apart.
What's that for?
Indigestion.
Look! I think he's arriving now.
Here. Okay.
[suave music playing]
[brakes squealing]
Hello, sir.
Let's go.
Um, excuse me, sir.
About the typhoon that hit Jeju…
It was pretty devastating.
I'm aware.
Sir, the damage assessment from the typhoon
has become quite substantial.
We appreciate that you built the buildings so sturdily
that the main facilities weren't affected.
But with the grounded flights and road blocks,
we've had many cancellations.
Our team is monitoring the financial impact.
Mm.
[clears throat]
These will be the specials on the menu this season.
Everything else can go.
[suave music resumes]
Sir, we're still working on the exact number of cancellations.
We'll report back by end of day.
Okay. What else?
Uh, according to our analysis,
it seems that we may not be able to meet TS Resort's sales goal
by the 30th anniversary.
That light is out.
[Rooms manager snaps]
Oh, yeah. We'll have that changed immediately.
[chuckles] We did manage
to get all the cancellation fees processed for the Jeju resort.
And the guests currently on-site have all requested to prolong their stays,
so we'll collect additional room fees from all of them.
[chuckles] So no need to worry about that, sir.
Really?
Yes, and those problematic guests who wouldn't pay the additional fees
were forcibly evicted.
[music fades]
Hm. And who was the one who made that decision?
Uh, it was General Manager Heo Ji-Hwan.
Ah-ha.
The general manager.
[suave music playing]
-Mr. Yoon. -Yes, sir.
You said we recently changed landscapers, right?
Yes, sir.
Change them again.
The layout is wrong.
Yes, agreed, sir.
[inhales deeply, sighs] Mr. Jang?
Uh, yes, sir?
Would you mind calling our general manager, please?
Yes, sir.
TS RESORT JEJU GENERAL MANAGER HEO JI-HWAN
-[outgoing call tone] -Hello, Mr. Heo?
[Heo] Yes, hello. How's everything going on your end?
Good. The Jeju resort has been in a state of emergency,
but you've handled the situation so well.
I'm calling because Director Baek personally wanted to speak to you.
[Heo] Oh, it was nothing.
As the general manager of the TS Resort in Jeju,
I had to take immediate action.
I have everything under control.
Yes. [chuckles]
Miss Go,
have you arrived yet?
Yes, we just got in, sir. Cameras are ready.
-[intriguing music playing] -[cameras clicking]
What are you doing?
Excuse me. Look right here, please. You're being recorded.
-What's going on? Get away! -Who gave you permission to film me? Huh?
-Why are you doing this? -Mr. Baek.
As you concluded, the general manager, Mr. Heo is holding some sort of meeting
with members of the golf club in one of the cancelled suites.
-Wait. -[woman] Okay.
-Mr. Baek confirmed he has the video. -And we've also secured the images.
-What? -[man] What the hell is this?
[Heo] Where did you guys even come from?
Was that clear enough?
Mr. Heo has been helping himself to the canceled suites.
Unauthorized, of course
and on the company dime.
-Is he insane? -Is this really news to you?
[Jang] Of course not!
Remove Mr. Heo from the premises and proceed with pressing charges.
Have the administrative team apologize to the guests who were forcibly evicted.
I'll take care of it right away
[Baek] I want you to open up all available rooms
to the victims of the typhoon at the Jeju resort,
and don't take any payments.
[both] What?
Oh, well, that's very nice of you.
[Baek] Oh.
You said we probably wouldn't be able to make our sales goal
for our 30th anniversary.
Well,
I think I can fix that.
[uplifting music playing]
WISHING A SWIFT RECOVERY AND RESTORATION TO THE TS RESORT TEAM
Right here, this way please.
We're not taking any reservations at the moment,
the rooms are booked for the victims of the typhoon.
[man] The power's out. You'll need to take the stairs.
Yeah, the lobby is completely full. Take your group to a different area. Okay?
[reporter] TS Resort Jeju has decided to open up the entire resort
to house the victims of the typhoon.
Senior Managing Director, Baek Ho-rang is heading the project,
which involves converting the rooms and lobby into emergency shelters.
He also plans to be heavily involved in the recovery efforts.
Updates on Jeju?
People with disabilities, pregnant women, and children
have been assigned suites.
Private accommodations have also been allocated
to individual guests and families.
And financial aid?
Yes, as you requested, all victims will have their stays comped for a month.
We've also decided to donate funds to the Jeju City Hall
and provide free relief supplies.
The media is praising your call to action and the public response is positive.
Our stock price has also gone up considerably.
I'm thinking we need to announce our new brand ambassador.
Have you found anyone?
Well…
[suave music playing]
…our first choice is the actor Ji Eun-ho.
He has the best reputation in the industry.
He's a rising star with idol-level fame
and is receiving endless offers to star in dramas and films.
WHEN THE SCHOOL BELL RINGS
TOP 10 SHOWS IN SOUTH KOREA
FOLLOWERS
JI EUN-HO "WORLDWIDE FAME FEELS UNREAL"
JI EUN-HO EMERGES AS A GLOBAL STAR
[Yoon] He recently won Best Actor at the Heuksang Arts Awards.
The drama he starred in was a massive hit.
He has an international fan base. He's even been cast in a Hollywood film.
So what's the problem?
Well, um… it's precisely for those reasons…
[sighs, inhales deeply]
…that we can't seem to get in touch with him.
[Baek sighs]
Mr. Yoon,
are you serious?
I can't do this anymore.
I'm already stressed out of my mind trying to manage the Jeju disaster,
now you're coming to me with this?
How are you supposed to sign him when you can't even get in touch with him?
What kind of update is that?
Why am I the only one who takes this seriously?
-[beeping] -[Yoon] Mr. Baek.
Mr. Baek.
Don't startle me like that.
You know my heart is weak.
You need to calm down.
Take a deep breath.
[Baek sighs]
Your pulse is above 100 beats per minute right now.
It's been doing that all the time lately.
Deep breath.
[exhales deeply]
-[Baek exhales deeply] -[calming music playing]
Empty your mind.
Let go of all your thoughts and worries.
[Baek exhales deeply]
And the impossible belief that you can control everything,
that obsession,
just let it go.
-[exhales deeply] -[Baek exhales deeply]
[sniffs]
[exhales deeply]
[music fades]
-Where is Ji Eun-ho right now? -What?
I'll find him
and sign him myself.
[sighs]
[woman sighs]
-[Bo-bae sighs] -Na.
-Oh, Seo-jeong. -Bo-bae.
-[elevator chimes] -[doors open]
[Seo-jeong sighs]
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[sighs] I can tell from that look that he chewed you out again.
What was it this time, the kiss or the romance?
-The kiss scene. -Oh boy.
How could Yeom expect anything else from a virgin?
-Someone could hear you. -[chuckles softly]
-Mm. -[Bo-bae sighs]
-[elevator clunks, powers down] -[Seo-jeong gasps]
Ugh, not again.
What? This one isn't working either.
Hey, why isn't anything working? Huh?
-I know. -[Seo-jeong groans]
Everything's broken. So annoying.
-What? -Bo-bae.
No, no, no, don't make me do it in public, please.
It's just me here. Who cares?
What about that?
No.
Oh, come on. Yeom will lose his mind if I'm late to run his errands.
Help a girl out, please.
[sighs]
Do this for me, and I'll tell you about this date I went on recently,
and I'll give you all the details.
[groans]
[Seo-jeong chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Bo-bae inhales deeply]
[exhales slowly]
[electricity crackling]
-[elevator clunks] -Ooh, whoa!
Damn. My little human Pikachu.
-Don't you call me that. I'm warning you. -[gasps]
Okay, okay. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Really, though, thanks Bo-bae.
Sorry.
[sighs]
The truth is, I've carried this secret with me for my entire life.
[intriguing music playing]
-[girl] What should we eat? -[boy] Hmm. I want a sundae.
-I want tteokbokki. -Then I want two bowls.
Then I want three.
Four for me, then.
[thunder rumbling]
[uneasy suspenseful music playing]
[thunder clapping]
[lightning crackling]
[dramatic music playing]
[Bo-bae] After I was struck by lightning,
I suddenly had the ability to control electricity.
-[crying] -[electricity crackling]
[breathing shakily] Bo-bae.
[gasps]
You must never… [shivers]
…touch anyone or make any physical contact.
[gasps]
[Bo-bae] Electricity started to flow through my body.
[intriguing music playing]
[screams] Ji-hye!
-A cockroach! -What? What's wrong?
There's a cockroach! Hurry up and catch it!
[screams] Ji-hye!
[Bo-bae] The more emotional I got, the stronger the electricity got too.
B… Bo-bae.
You said that you wanted to be with me.
You guys haven't even made it official.
I mean, come on, he told me you won't even let him hold your hand.
[Bo-bae gasps]
How could you tell her?
What do you expect me to do?
You wouldn't let me tell you how I feel, let alone touch you.
What guy would put up with something like that, huh?
[sad, wistful music playing]
[glass shattering]
[electricity crackling]
[Bo-bae] So I ended up completely alone,
thanks to this stupid power of mine.
[elevator chimes]
You could try to smile.
Whoa, whoa. What's with the crowd?
Hey, I think a celebrity is here or something. Put your gloves on.
See ya.
I'll call you after work to kiss and tell.
Thanks, you pain in the butt. [groans]
[gasps] Ah.
[winces, stomach gurgles]
Ow. What's wrong with me?
[groaning softly]
[indistinct murmuring]
I didn't consider this.
What if the press sees me?
[Yoon] I don't think any of them
are reporters.
[Baek] Hmm.
ONY AND ONLY EUN-HO
JI EUN-HO
Hm. Let's go.
[clears throat]
[intriguing music playing]
[girl 1 gasps] Oh. Oh, my God it's Eun-ho!
-Whoa, let's go over there, hurry up! -[girls squealing]
[Yoon] Mr. Baek. Mr. Baek. Sir, be careful. Mr. Baek.
[camera shutter clicking]
Mr. Baek. Mr. Baek. Ah, sir, be careful.
Argh.
Mr. Baek!
[girls screaming]
Ah! Thanks so much. Thanks so much. Means a lot.
Mr. Baek! No!
Thanks so much! Thanks, everyone.
[girls screaming in distance]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music fades slowly]
[kissing]
[soaring romantic music playing]
[music fades]
[girls screaming]
That…
Uh…
[hesitates] Are you okay?
Oh, uh, uh, yeah.
I'm sorry the crowd pushed me.
Mm. Uh, I know. It's okay.
-All right, then. Uh, so sorry about that. -Oh, sure, yeah.
[gasps]
-Huh? [gasps] -[intriguing music playing]
[Yoon] Sir!
Mr. Baek! Excuse me, sorry.
-[sighs] -[rapid footsteps approach]
-Wait! Hold on, wait. Please! -[gasps]
[panting]
Wait… [chuckles]
Hi there.
[breathes heavily]
[gasps] Oh.
[squeaky toy squeak]
Uh. Hey!
[gasps]
Nothing's happening.
What should happen?
Um… [clears throat]
Uh, earlier when our lips touched, did you feel anything?
Like maybe a prickling sensation or a spark?
[Baek scoffs]
No, no spark for me.
If you'll excuse me.
Hi. Sorry, but… [chuckles]
-What are you-- -Can I just…
-What are you doing? -Oh.
-Wait, hold on! -Why are you doing that?
Just. Please let me…
-Stop what you're doing. -Just once. Come on. [grunting]
I just need to see…
[grunting]
Mr. Yoon!
-Mr. Yoon! -Oh, Mr. Baek! Mr. Baek!
[girls screaming]
[gasps]
[chuckles] Still nothing.
It can't be.
Is this guy immune to my electrical powers?
Like a human rubber glove?
Sorry.
-[exhales deeply] -What?
Do you think
that we could give it one more go?
-[Yoon] Mr. Baek! -[Bo-bae gasps]
[pants] Please tell me you haven't been hurt.
[Baek shudders]
[chuckles]
-Do you know this woman? -I, uh… don't know her.
I'm not interested, so please leave me alone.
No… [hesitates] That's not what… Ah.
-Oh. Can we talk for a second. -[elevator chimes]
Just please, can I? [grunts]
I just need to talk to you. It'll only take a second. Please.
[shushes] You better not lay a finger on him.
-Wait, no… [pants] -[electricity crackles]
-[pained grunt] -Oh no. Are you okay?
-[gasps] -[jaunty music playing]
Then why was there no spark with him?
-[gasps] -[gasps]
Ah. Argh.
-What? -Ah! [pained yelling]
-Ah! -What's wrong?
-My stomach… Oh, sorry! -[electricity crackles]
[pained yelling] Oh, my stomach hurts!
[pained crying]
Sorry. I…
Could you please help me find that man, my human rubber glove?
-[paramedic] Does that hurt? -[pained yelling]
Let's get you to the hospital right away.
[sobbing] No!
[siren wailing]
119 EMERGENCY MEDICAL SERVICES
Look. Whoa. Wonder what happened.
The woman in the ambulance
looked like Bo-bae, don't you think?
Na Bo-bae?
Why would she be here?
Well, she could've been here for work, you know?
-[inhales] I'm gonna call her. -Eun-ho, don't bother with that.
You know how important today's meeting is right?
-Yeah. -If you disappear on me, I'm dead.
Just call her after the meeting, okay?
-Damn, I keep dropping all this. -She's not picking up.
-Something's wrong. -Hey!
Hey, hey, Ji Eun-ho!
Here we go.
Ji Eun-ho, where are you going? The director is waiting for you!
[gentle music playing]
[music fades]
[sighs]
Maybe something came up. He's not usually late.
You told me you'd be able to get me a meeting with Ji Eun-ho
whenever I wanted, yet Ji Eun-ho is nowhere to be found.
Well, I guess I'll mark this down as a coffee date between friends.
[chuckles awkwardly] Oh, yes.
[Baek sighs]
It's been so nice to have some one-on-one time, my friend.
-Mr. Yoon. -[Yeom] Ho-rang…
I mean, Mr. Baek. Mr. Baek! Just wait. Please, hold on.
I'll do whatever it takes. I'm going to get another meeting.
All I need is for you to put in a good word for me at TS Resort.
They're telling me they're no longer letting us film on location.
Did your proposal include any alternatives?
Alternatives?
If your schedule was planned efficiently, you would've had a backup plan,
and they would've said yes.
Ho-rang, we're old college friends.
Come on, I'm on my knees here.
If I was going to do all that paperwork, there'd be no point in asking.
Getting me that meeting with him was the only condition
for me helping you with location approval.
But Ji Eun-ho isn't here, as you can see.
-Hey, Ho-rang. -[door opens]
-[door closes] -[sighs]
Heartless bastard. What kind of backup plan?
I'll have Plan A, B, C, D. The whole damn alphabet while I'm at it.
You and your stupid backup plan.
[dance music playing]
[clubbers cheering]
Shit. Take a look at this, you fucking bastards!
[Ho-rang] "TS Hotel's Choi Do-Yoon Caught Drunk Swearing at Club."
"'You effing bastards.'"
Look at that.
"TS Hotel is facing public backlash following this incident."
"TS Hotel has been eliminated
from this year's list of finest-ranking hotels
and its subsidiary, TS Resort,
has also seen a dramatic decline in domestic sales rankings."
[sighs, scoffs]
[tense music playing]
I work to elevate the company's image, and he drags it back down.
I feel like we're playing a game of tug-of-war. [sighs]
[sighs deeply]
[music fades]
Find out where Ji Eun-ho is. I need to meet him in person.
Meet him today?
Sir, you really need to get to the hospital after the temple.
Plan A was for you to sign Ji Eun-ho, but you failed on that front.
Plan B was for me to convince him today, but that plan fell through as well.
Tell me, what do we do now?
We go to Plan C, sir.
Plan C is for you to find him so I can meet him myself.
This needs to happen today, because I pushed my surgery again.
But you still--
And if we don't meet him today, Plan D is to postpone the surgery indefinitely.
Yes, understood, Mr. Baek.
I'll find him today.
And contact a good ad agency as well.
But before any of that,
pay your respects to your sister.
[pensive music playing]
[Ho-rang sighs]
You're here.
Did you come to see your parents?
Yes, I thought they'd be happy to hear that tomorrow will be my last surgery.
THE LATE BAEK GYEONG-SEOK THE LATE RYU MIN-SEON
Did you see what Do-yoon did?
That brat is a lost cause.
Are you positive this surgery is going to make you normal?
Well, I am already normal.
Just make sure you come back completely healthy this time.
If you give them any sign of weakness,
it'll make the succession process difficult.
It's important to present yourself as the perfect leader,
just like your parents did.
[uneasy music playing]
[woman] Miss!
Miss!
-Excuse me, miss. -What?
[whimpers] Mr. Baek isn't in here. I'm sorry.
Where is he?
His schedule is confidential, even to members of his family. Apologies.
Hey. Do I look like I'm here as a part of his family?
I'm here as the CEO of TS Hotel. Check his schedule again!
My name has to be there.
[sighs] I'm so sorry.
I don't care if you're sorry!
Check it again now!
-Hey, Mom! Come on. -I can't…
How could you yell at such a beautiful young lady?
I'm so sorry if she scared you.
She's going through the life change right now.
[grunts, chuckles]
[inhales deeply] So,
where is my one and only cousin?
Yeah, got it. I'll call you right away.
Yes, I'm sure. Okay.
[call disconnect beeps]
Mr. Baek.
Mrs. Baek Gyeong-jin and Mr. Choi Do-yoon are at your office as we speak.
[inhales deeply] Of all the days to pay me a visit at work…
[sighs] That's my family for you.
Speaking of, did you say hi to your sister?
Yes, thank you for asking, Mr. Baek. It was good catching up.
And I was able to track down Mr. Ji Eun-ho.
-He's at Taesung Hospital. -Taesung Hospital?
He's not a patient.
He went to see someone there, after our meeting earlier.
We'll see Dr. Jang while we're at the hospital.
Sounds great.
[indistinct chattering]
[pensive music playing]
-[gasps] -[gasps]
Still nothing. [gasps]
All right, up next…
Oh! It's Ji Eun-ho! Yeah!
-He looks just like my grandson. -[woman 1] Oh please.
The only thing those two have in common are a mouth, two eyes and a nose.
-[chuckling] -He really does look like him!
-[woman 1] You say that about everyone. -[laughter]
-It's so nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
I'm so happy I'm finally able to meet you in person.
I know I'm such a fan of yours, Jaejae,
I've always wanted to be a guest on your show.
-Really, I'm truly honored to be here. -Wow.
Well, as expected from the king of romance,
you've truly mastered sweet talking.
So you're known for romances
and, of course, your breakout role was in a youth drama.
That's right.
You made your debut in the drama Wistful Youth.
And you still say it's your favorite work to date, right?
[Eun-ho] Yes, exactly.
[Jaejae] When I heard you were coming on,
I made sure to binge-watch everything you were in.
And wow, that one was a true masterpiece. I cried my eyes out.
-Wow, thanks so much. -Just incredible.
That project felt like the real beginning of my acting career.
To my writer, hope you're watching.
[Jaejae] Wow, that's one lucky writer.
Oh, what's he doing?
Bo-bae.
-[gasps] -Ooh!
Oh, what are you? Hey. Eun-ho! Oh…
[woman 2] Wait a minute!
Eun-ho, how on earth did you know I was here?
[sighs] Is there anything about you I don't know?
You should stop eating takeout, Bo-bae. That's probably why you're here.
Ugh, that's not why I'm in the hospital. It's just my appendix.
-Appendix? Did it burst? -Mm.
Then you need surgery immediately. I'll get a doctor.
Eun-ho, wait. [gasps painfully]
[winces, moans]
[Eun-ho breathing heavily]
-Excuse me. -Mm, what? [gasps]
Ji Eun… You're Ji Eun-ho right?
Right. There's a patient here whose named Na Bo-bae, you know?
-[nurse] Oh, Na Bo-bae? -Yeah.
Mr. Ji Eun-ho?
[intriguing music playing]
TS RESORT SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR
So the meeting with Mr. Yeom was actually for you?
Yes. I asked him not to say anything. I didn't want to make you feel pressured.
Well, sorry I missed our meeting.
A friend of mine became ill. I should actually head back now.
Don't worry.
This hospital is part of the TS Group, so if you give me the patient's name,
I will make sure they get the very best care.
Have them moved to the VIP room.
Here is the deal. In return, I'd like you to make room in your schedule for us.
Mr. Baek, please direct all work-related questions to my agent.
We'll accommodate all of your reasonable requests, Mr. Ji.
[chuckles] Well, you see…
Send the patient's coordinates, name and date of birth
to the number on my business card.
The TS Group is a wonderful company to work with.
You'll see that this is just the first taste of that.
[sighs] Wow, what a pain in my butt.
[clicks teeth]
-[man] Oh, where is this kid? -[sighs]
-Huh? Hey, you brat! -You scared me!
-Come with me. -Five more minutes.
-What do you mean? -I can't go now.
-Five more minutes. -Why are you here in the first place?
Hey. Sorry, something came up.
When's the surgery?
Jeez. Come on. Why are you so obsessed with this girl?
Hm, okay. I'll come visit you tomorrow, then.
Get some rest.
Yep.
Going where? Your schedule is completely full.
And why did you run out of our meeting earlier?
Do you know how much I had to apologize?
Hee-chan.
Did you know the plan was for me to meet Mr. Baek Ho-rang instead of the Director?
What? I don't know this Bacon guy. I have no idea.
[Eun-ho inhales deeply, sighs]
Come on. I told you I was fine with promoting my movies,
but I'm not comfortable selling my image for ad campaigns.
-You promised me you'd refuse those. -Well, I thought I did.
-Guess I don't have much pull anymore. -[sighs]
Don't let it happen again, okay?
[Ho-rang] Let's find out who Eun-ho was visiting earlier.
-[Yoon] Yes, sir. -[Bo-bae gasps] Excuse me.
[jaunty music playing]
[gasps] You again!
[gasps]
I've been thinking about you since we met.
[gasps] Did you come all this way for me?
You really need to stop.
Oh, so I guess the spark just hit you now?
I felt no spark at all. Absolutely nothing.
That's just so… [gasps] …amazing!
-Step aside. -[Bo-bae chuckles]
-[chuckles] -[Yoon] Please move. [groans]
Whoa! Sorry. Uh, sorry! I'm so sorry.
[gasps painfully]
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Just wait a second, please.
Look. [grunts]
This is going to sound really weird, I know.
But you're the first person I've ever met who's like a rubber glove. [gasps]
Can we talk, sir? [grunts]
-No. I'm too busy. -[Bo-bae grunts]
Uh, in that case, your number, just your number.
Please your phone number.
If now's not a good time, I can text you a detailed explanation instead.
Oh, please. Can you just hear me out for one more second?
[sighs, inhales]
All right. [sighs]
Um…
Mm. What's your name?
[relieved sigh] Na Bo-bae.
Na Bo-bae?
[chuckles]
I've heard plenty of pickup lines in my day,
but your pathetic attempt at flirting?
-That's a first. -[disappointed musical sting plays]
You think I'm flirting with you?
Accidentally bumping lips with a handsome guy
who obviously has money.
Are you that desperate that you talk about love with a stranger?
Even if I did touch you,
I wouldn't feel a spark, a buzz, absolutely nothing at all.
So stop wasting my time.
Now, please get out!
-[Bo-bae gasps] -[Ho-rang grunts]
[sighs] What?
-[Ho-rang sighs] -Well done, Mr. Baek.
Mr. Yoon, how is it you couldn't stop a lone woman in a hospital?
Well, I, uh… She kept giving me static shocks.
I'm sorry, sir.
-It's just… -What?
Forget it.
I'm just saying, I've never seen you be so harsh to a stranger before.
What, you… I wasn't really that bad, was I?
Well, you were simply being honest and direct.
Just like you are with me. You were totally harsh, Mr. Baek.
-[whimsical music playing] -Well, she's out of her mind!
Talking about how I'm the first person she could ever really fall in love with.
But she didn't say love.
-Yes, she did. -No, she didn't.
I'm sorry, but she said you were like a rubber glove, sir.
-So you heard her say it too? -Yes.
She must have misspoken. Love makes much more sense.
Why on earth would she say rubber glove?
Well, good point.
[Ho-rang sighs]
[knocking on door]
-Yes? -[door opens]
Oh! Hey, Ho-rang. You're here!
-[laughs] -Yes, at last.
-[Dr. Jang] Ah. Glad you made it. -[chuckles]
[sighs]
Oh! [chuckles]
Cute, huh?
Kissing gouramis.
Look! Look at them! They actually kiss. [chuckles]
[pensive music playing]
You call that a kiss? I'm not falling for that one again.
Ha!
[squeaky toy squeak]
Sorry, what? What?
Ah, nothing. Uh…
The battery?
Ah! [chuckles]
Yes.
This is a brand-new battery model that just came out in the US.
This technology clearly surpasses any of the old artificial hearts.
[chuckles]
And since we're replacing the entire device,
we'll need to make a bigger incision in your chest,
but this will certainly last 100 years.
A battery that lasts a whole century. Guess it'll outlive me.
[sighs] I'm just saying you won't have to replace it again.
[chuckles]
I give you my word.
This is the last time I'll be operating on you.
And the day after tomorrow,
I will start working on my plan to take over the company.
[hopeful music playing]
So take good care of me, Doctor.
The surgery's scheduled early tomorrow, so get some rest, Ho-rang.
[chuckles softly]
-[glasses clink] -[all] Cheers.
[dance music pumping in distance]
I heard Hanlim Advertising Agency landed TS Resort's new promo.
[man 1] Wow, Hanlim's on a roll.
Seems like the company's been doing great since Seol-hee was promoted to director.
[man 2] Yeah, that's because my Seol-hee is so incredibly good at her job.
Seol-hee,
how do you like the wine?
This one's a fine Romani--
[Do-yoon] Hey, bro!
Pour me another.
[chuckles]
More.
Whoo! More.
-Slow down. This wine should be savored… -Show me how much you love me!
[sighs]
[inhales sharply] I see.
Not loving me so much after all.
Asshole, there's not much left.
I get it now. It's not that Si-hun's not feeling generous.
It's just that the size of this glass is working against him.
You can't even manage to fill it up.
What the hell!
[Do-yoon] Si-hun, if you plan on seducing a woman,
maybe try to put in more effort.
Don't be so cheap.
Oh, Seol-hee, you're coming home with me, okay?
No, I'm going home alone.
Seol-hee!
-Get in. -I don't get into cars with drunk drivers.
Goodbye, Do-yoon.
Mm. Fine I'll call us a driver.
What?
You have nothing to say? Huh?
Even about how well I did? Hm?
You didn't have to embarrass him like that.
Si-hun didn't know his place and he was trying to hit on you.
-But so are you, Do-yoon. -You're hurting my feelings here.
You're telling me that cook and I are in the same league? Are you kidding?
[chuckles]
I mean, he might stir pots, but you book beds.
What's the difference?
At least make sure you're the heir to the TS Group
if you're going to talk status.
[sniffs]
Han Seol-hee,
you know Baek Ho-rang
isn't interested in marrying you.
He couldn't care less about you.
Okay. Call yourself a driver.
You wouldn't want another embarrassing headline
because of a DUI, would you?
[uneasy music playing]
[tires screeching]
[thunder clapping]
[intriguing music playing]
[Dr. Jang] Okay, if everyone's ready, we can begin.
Scalpel.
HEMODIALYSIS UNIT
-[electricity crackling] -Ow, that hurt!
Oh, I told you not to touch me with your bare hands.
You should always wear your gloves.
-[thunder clapping] -[gasps]
[thunder clapping]
[nurse 1] Okay, okay.
Huh?
[intriguing music continues]
[thunder clapping]
-[doctor 1] Did the power go out? -[doctor 2] What about emergency power?
There's a problem. The emergency power isn't coming on.
It'll take three minutes for the generator to start.
-Turn the crank manually! -[doctor 3] Okay!
-[tense music playing] -[mechanical whirring]
Okay, slowly.
Um, excuse me. Hold on. Can you really perform surgery in the dark?
Wait. Don't hospitals have some kind of backup power during a blackout?
I'm a little scared. I'm not gonna die during an appendectomy, right?
Don't worry, Miss Na. The generator will kick in soon.
[Bo-bae whimpers]
[music building]
[dramatic music stabs]
[tense music continues]
OPERATING ROOM
Oh, I think I'm the one who's making the lights go on.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
Oh, the power is coming back because of me.
[machine beeping]
-[doctor 2] He's in cardiac arrest. -[doctor 1] Another milliliter of epi!
[machine flatlining]
[rhythmic beeping]
-[music fades] -[doctor 1] Vitals are normal.
-Blood pressure is good. 120 over 80. -Okay. Reduce flow.
Let's close him up.
[groans tiredly]
[uneasy music playing]
[music fades]
[intriguing music playing]
[gasps]
What?
What is he doing in my room? [gasps]
[softly] Hello?
[grunts]
Hello?
[music fades]
[intriguing music resumes]
Ow!
Hello?
[music fades]
Oh, this is weird.
My electric charge has no effect on him? [gasps]
If this guy really is my rubber glove,
that means that I can actually touch him
and maybe even… date him?
[tinkling romantic music playing]
[music intensifies]
[romantic Korean ballad playing]
[music fades out]